<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Kevin Cawley</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Kevin Cawley</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Template © Edna West</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 10:27:30 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learning HTML and CSS</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/learning_html_css/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 10:27:30 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/learning_html_css/</guid><description>In the spring of 2021 I was assigned to help create the TARDIS website. In order to do this I had to learn both the basics of HTML and CSS, which I did using the website internetting is hard.
I learned about positioning, displays, margings, and interactive elements. After I finished all of the website modules I went on to my first task, which was the creation of this website in order to put my skills to the test.</description></item><item><title>My First Solo Project</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/my-first-large-project/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 12:20:37 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/my-first-large-project/</guid><description>My first solo project was in documentation. I had been working on fixing up documentation errors that were present on GitHub issues, when I got ready to tackle two large issues: the creation of documentation and coding guidelines for TARDIS.
This was a large step up in importance, as I would be setting guidelines for how all code past and future should be written. It would also make it so that documentation issues like the ones I had been working on for the past month wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be repeated.</description></item><item><title>Working With Documentation</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/working-with-documentation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 11:40:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/working-with-documentation/</guid><description>As a result of my somewhat slow results and my basic knowledge of Python at the time, I was put onto the documentation for TARDIS. TARDIS documentation is very cohesive, but there were issues mostly regarding formatting and the style of documentation, specifically with regards to docstrings. There was old syntax present that would mess with the TARDIS documentation pages, so I read through all of the modules going around fixing the docstrings.</description></item><item><title>First Interactions with TARDIS</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/first-interactions-with-tardis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 10:48:23 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/first-interactions-with-tardis/</guid><description>My first introduction to TARDIS was due to my involvement in the Professorial Assistantship program at MSU, which allowed me as a freshman to start doing research. I was placed with TARDIS due to my interest in understanding how the world works and my enjoyment of math.
After I had finished my crash course of Python 2 (TARDIS is written in Python 3, but Python 2 was free) through CodeAcademy, I was given my first task.</description></item><item><title>Learning Python</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/learning_python/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 10:48:23 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/learning_python/</guid><description>This is a walkthrough of my Python projects that I did in my CSE231 class, and I will discuss what new features each project included from the next.
I started coding in the Fall of 2020 in CSE 231: Introduction to Programming I. This is a course in Python, and is meant for people who have little to no experience in coding like I was.
CSE 231 covered a large part of Python.</description></item><item><title>First Experience with Coding</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/first-experience-with-coding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 10:27:30 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/post/first-experience-with-coding/</guid><description>Python was the first coding language I ever learned. I started learning it in the Fall of 2020 in my Introduction to Computer Programming class. I learned Python 3.0, and used Spyder to work with Python. Spyder had an Editor, Debugger, Variable Explorer, and Shell all in one. It was a very contained experience which made it easy for me. I found the Shell fun because I could test out code by writing it directly into the shell to see the results instead of having to write a program and then run it.</description></item></channel></rss>