<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio on Kevin Cawley</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolio on Kevin Cawley</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Template © Edna West</copyright><atom:link href="https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Music</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/music/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/music/</guid><description>I got interested in the harp in music class. In thirs grade I was flipping through my music textbook and saw a page that had pictures of the harp through the centuries, from the Egyptian harp with as few as 5 strings to the modern double-action concert grand with 47 strings. I remember going home and declaring that I was going to play the harp, much to my parents amusement. After all, when a 9-year-old says something like that, how serious can it be.</description></item><item><title>Python Projects</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/python_projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/python_projects/</guid><description>This is a walkthrough of my Python projects that I did in my CSE231 class, and I will discuss what new features each project included from the next.
I started coding in the Fall of 2020 in CSE 231: Introduction to Programming I. This is a course in Python, and is meant for people who have little to no experience in coding like I was.
CSE 231 covered a large part of Python.</description></item><item><title>TARDIS</title><link>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/tardis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kevincawley.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/tardis/</guid><description>TARDIS is an open-source code whose purpose is to create
fast and accurate synthesis of supernovae spectra while only requiring a few input parameters. These parameters can be modified and turned on/off to allow TARDIS to be used for different applications. Different models can be created by changing the concentration of elements, selecting different physics approximations and measurements, and other features.</description></item></channel></rss>